{
  "questions": [
    
      {
        "question": "10 - 3 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "7",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "6", "9", "5" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "15 - 4 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "11",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "12", "10", "13" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "20 - 8 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "12",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "10", "15", "18" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "25 - 6 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "19",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "20", "18", "22" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "30 - 7 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "23",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "22", "25", "20" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "35 - 9 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "26",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "25", "27", "28" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "40 - 12 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "28",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "26", "30", "32" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "45 - 15 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "30",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "32", "28", "35" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "50 - 18 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "32",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "30", "35", "28" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "55 - 20 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "30", "40", "25" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "60 - 25 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "30", "40", "45" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "65 - 30 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "70 - 35 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "75 - 40 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "80 - 45 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "85 - 50 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "90 - 55 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "95 - 60 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "100 - 65 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      },
      {
        "question": "105 - 70 = ?",
        "correctAnswer": "35",
        "wrongAnswers": [ "40", "45", "50" ]
      }
  ]
}